[{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980419707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":21101,"timeElapsed":83037},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980431946,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":12237,"timeElapsed":95276},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980449007,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":17059,"timeElapsed":112337},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980465853,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":16844,"timeElapsed":129183},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980476506,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":10651,"timeElapsed":139836},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980490391,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":13884,"timeElapsed":153721},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980495995,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5602,"timeElapsed":159325},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980504191,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":8194,"timeElapsed":167521},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980510835,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":6643,"timeElapsed":174165},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980542765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":29293,"timeElapsed":206095},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980552879,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":10113,"timeElapsed":216209},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980568024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":15143,"timeElapsed":231354},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980573334,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":5308,"timeElapsed":236664},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980577574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4238,"timeElapsed":240904},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980582133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4558,"timeElapsed":245463},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980585579,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3444,"timeElapsed":248909},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980594079,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":8498,"timeElapsed":257409},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980598058,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"198","question":"Do you know any “party tricks”? If so, describe them. If not, describe one you would like to learn.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3978,"timeElapsed":261388},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980639863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":38817,"timeElapsed":303193},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980654208,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":14344,"timeElapsed":317538},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980658413,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":4204,"timeElapsed":321743},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980666908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":8493,"timeElapsed":330238},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980671970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":5061,"timeElapsed":335300},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980675553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3581,"timeElapsed":338883},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980679681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":4126,"timeElapsed":343011},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980686004,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":6322,"timeElapsed":349334},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980689384,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3378,"timeElapsed":352714},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980702067,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":10869,"timeElapsed":365397},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980707282,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":5214,"timeElapsed":370612},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980714928,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":7644,"timeElapsed":378258},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980724482,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":9553,"timeElapsed":387812},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980729077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":4593,"timeElapsed":392407},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980733237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4159,"timeElapsed":396567},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980736727,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3488,"timeElapsed":400057},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980742627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":5899,"timeElapsed":405957},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980745472,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2844,"timeElapsed":408802},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980761506,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":12578,"timeElapsed":424836},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980766362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4854,"timeElapsed":429692},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980772492,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":6129,"timeElapsed":435822},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980775337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2843,"timeElapsed":438667},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980779762,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4424,"timeElapsed":443092},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980795987,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":16223,"timeElapsed":459317},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980801560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5571,"timeElapsed":464889},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980805127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3566,"timeElapsed":468457},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980808881,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3753,"timeElapsed":472211},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980823847,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":13158,"timeElapsed":487177},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980827071,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":3222,"timeElapsed":490401},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980831885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4813,"timeElapsed":495215},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980845505,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":13618,"timeElapsed":508835},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980853047,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":7540,"timeElapsed":516377},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980856961,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":3912,"timeElapsed":520290},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980863692,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":6729,"timeElapsed":527021},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980867245,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3551,"timeElapsed":530575},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980870945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3699,"timeElapsed":534275},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980875885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4938,"timeElapsed":539215},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980890025,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":11920,"timeElapsed":553355},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980893176,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3149,"timeElapsed":556506},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980902530,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":9353,"timeElapsed":565860},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980906385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3854,"timeElapsed":569715},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980914693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8306,"timeElapsed":578023},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980918339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3644,"timeElapsed":581669},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980929709,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":11368,"timeElapsed":593039},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980939255,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":9544,"timeElapsed":602585},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980945179,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":5922,"timeElapsed":608509},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980948622,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":3442,"timeElapsed":611952},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980960160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":8634,"timeElapsed":623490},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980964945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":4784,"timeElapsed":628275},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980969247,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":4300,"timeElapsed":632577},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980976198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":6950,"timeElapsed":639528},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980980741,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":4542,"timeElapsed":644071},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980984820,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4077,"timeElapsed":648150},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980988458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3637,"timeElapsed":651788},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980991968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3509,"timeElapsed":655298},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980996215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"29","question":"What, if anything, is too serious to be joked about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":4245,"timeElapsed":659545},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981026501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":28607,"timeElapsed":689831},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981029148,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2645,"timeElapsed":692478},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981034940,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":5790,"timeElapsed":698270},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981037602,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2661,"timeElapsed":700932},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981043294,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5690,"timeElapsed":706624},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981046802,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3507,"timeElapsed":710132},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981054999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":8196,"timeElapsed":718329},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981059298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":4297,"timeElapsed":722628},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981062288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2988,"timeElapsed":725618},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981069392,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":5342,"timeElapsed":732722},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981072703,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":3309,"timeElapsed":736033},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981077147,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":4442,"timeElapsed":740477},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981080628,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3479,"timeElapsed":743957},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981083818,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3189,"timeElapsed":747148},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981086667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2847,"timeElapsed":749997},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981091514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":4845,"timeElapsed":754843},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981094952,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":3437,"timeElapsed":758282},{"subjectID":"tlw5wldwms","prolificID":"673a0fa7ed1b0189b74d67db","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25ac9e189f44da6fa19","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981097642,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":2688,"timeElapsed":760972}]